Previously on Friends:
上集回顧：
-How did the job stuff go? -He offered me one!
-工作的事怎麼樣？ -他給了我一份工作
You know what? This calls for a bottle of lsrael's finest!
這時候該來一瓶以色列的佳釀
The job is in Paris.
工作是在巴黎
Oh, God, please, somebody say something.
天啊, 你們說話呀
So if you take this job, you'll be moving to Paris?
如果你接受這份工作 你將要搬去巴黎嗎？
Or facing a bitch of a commute.
難道是乘飛機上下班？
I know, it's huge, and it's scary and it's really far away from you guys.
我明白這很艱巨, 我感到恐懼 而且離你們那麼那麼的遙遠
But this is such an incredible opportunity for me.
可是這對我是一個很好的機會
I've already told them about our situation with Emma..
我還跟他們說明了艾瑪的情況
and they said they'll do whatever we need to make us feel comfortable.
他們答應盡力給予我方便
I mean, I'll fly back and forth, they'll fly you out. Anything we want.
我可以回來看望她, 你也可以帶她去看望我  滿足我們任何要求
My boss said I might be getting a new lamp in my cubicle.
我老闆答應給我的睡房買一盞新的檯燈
-All right. We'll work it out. -Oh, thank you. Thank you.
-好的, 沒問題  -謝謝
-You sure this is what you want? -I think it is.
-這是你渴望的嗎？ -我相信是
-What's going on? -I got a really incredible job offer.
-怎麼了？ -我得到一份很棒的工作
-Hey, great! All right! -Good for you!
-太好了  -為你高興
-It's in Paris. -What?
-是在巴黎  -什麼？
No, no, no! No, no, no! No, too much is changing, okay?
不 不 不 發生太多改變了
First Phoebe getting married. Congratulations.
首先 菲比結婚了 恭喜
And then these two move in to a stupid house in the stupid suburbs.
然後這兩個傢伙要搬到 那所討厭的房子
-Earlier, you said you'd be supportive. -It comes and goes. I wouldn't trust it!
-嘿, 今天下午你還說會支持的  -我變來變去的, 不能相信我
You guys, this is really, really important to me.
夥計們, 這對我十分十分重要
It means a lot if you could try to get onboard.
如果你們嘗試接受, 我會很感激的
-Of course we can. Congratulations. -Thank you.
-我們當然會 恭喜你  -謝謝
Joey?
喬伊
No, my hugs are reserved for people staying in America!
我的擁抱只給留在美國的那些人
Joey, it would mean..
喬伊, 我
No! Get your France-going arms away from me!
不, 要去法國的人別靠近我
-Are you okay with this? -Well, it makes me feel sad, but..
-你不會難過吧  -實際上我感到傷心
-Talking to Ross. -I see.
-我是在問羅斯 -知道了
Rachel moving to another country? Not being able to see her every day?
瑞秋去了另一個國家 不能每天看到她？
How could I be okay with this?
我怎麼會不難過！？
But what are we gonna do? She really needs this job.
我們又能怎麼樣？她需要這份工作
Do you think if Ralph Lauren offered her her old job back, she would take it?
如果拉夫.勞倫公司請她回去, 她會願意嗎？
How's that gonna happen?
這怎麼可能？
Is this the best way to use one of your three magic wishes?
你就是這麼使用你的3個魔法願望的嗎？
Like, I don't know, I could talk to her boss. Yeah.
也許, 我能跟她的老闆談談
I met him at that Christmas party. I mean, we really hit it off.
對, 我跟他在聖誕派對見過面  我們相處的很好
-The guy who kept calling you "Ron"? -I didn't say we were brothers!
-是一直管你叫Ron的那個傢伙嗎？ -我並沒有說我們是兄弟呀
Technically, this is not a hug.
技術上說, 這不算擁抱
The One Where Estelle Dies
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
You read the obituaries?
你讀過訃告了?
Yeah. Well, I got a few curses on people.
是的, 而且, 我受到一些人的詛咒
I just like to see how they're coming.
我只想看看他們怎麼來
-Hey, Phoebe. Hey. -Hi.
-嘿, 菲比 -嘿
The house next door to the one that we're buying just went on the market.
在我們打算買的那座房子旁邊, 有一座房子也在出售
I wanna take a look at it, but Chandler doesn't.
我想去看看, 可錢德不願意
We close escrow tomorrow.
我們明天就簽約了
Seeing another house can only confuse us. We're easily confused.
再看其它房子只會迷惑自己  我們很容易感到迷惑
We're not very bright.
我們並不機靈
But what if it's better than ours? Shouldn't we look?
那如果它比我們的更好呢 至少應該看看
What do you think, Phoebe?
你怎麼看, 菲比？
Well, I think that shirt makes you look like you should work at a Baskin-Robbins.
我覺得你穿這件襯衣 像雪糕餐廳的服務員
Anyway..
反正怎麼都像
-Hey, isn't Joey's agent Estelle Leonard? -Yeah.
-喬伊的經理人是Estelle Lenord嗎？ -對.
-She died. -You're kidding!
-她死了  -真的嗎？
-That's terrible. -Yeah, last Saturday.
-真糟糕  -是的, 在上個星期
Wow! She was the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic!
哇！她是第一個獨自駕機 飛越大西洋的黑人男性
-Wait a minute, I read the wrong one. -Oh, yeah?
-哦, 等等 我看錯了另一個  -哦？
-Yeah, she was just an agent. -Joey's gonna be so upset.
-她只是一個經理人  -喬伊肯定感到很難過
I know. He always wanted to be the first black man to cross the Atlantic.
是的 他一直希望成為 第一個獨自駕機飛越大西洋的黑人男性
We cannot tell Joey about this.
我們不能讓喬伊知道這件事
He's already flipping out about everything changing.
一切都在改變, 他都快要發瘋了
This'll push him over the edge.
不能再刺激他了
-You don't think we should tell him? -Not for a while.
-你真的認為我們不應該告訴他嗎？ -至少暫時不說
Let's just give him a few days to get used to everything else.
給他幾天, 先消化已經發生了的事
What if he reads the paper?
如果他從報紙上看到呢？
Unless Snoopy says it to Charlie Brown, I think we're okay.
除非是八卦的史努比告訴查理布朗 否則就沒問題
-May I help you? -Yeah. I'm a friend of Rachel Green's.
-有什麼事嗎？ -我是瑞秋格林的朋友
Actually, we met at the Christmas party about two years ago.
我們2年前在聖誕派對上見過面
-Oh, right. Don? -Close. Ron.
-哦, 是Don？ -差不多, 是Ron
Well, what can I do for you?
有什麼能幫忙的嗎？
Well, I'm here to see if you'll give Rachel her job back.
想瞭解一下, 能不能恢復瑞秋的工作？
Did she ask you to come here and do this?
是她讓他來的嗎？
First I have to get you to agree..
不 如果你同意了
then we'll see if she wants to come back.
我還要問問她是否願意回來
Wow, that is tempting.
哇, 這真吸引人
She loved her job here. Let's face it, you're not gonna find anyone..
她很喜歡這份工作 實際上你找不到比她更好的人選
who did it as well as she did. Isn't that true?
是這樣嗎？
-She is good. -I took a shot there.
-她是很不錯  -我真沒料到
But I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do.
可是, 很抱歉 我無能為力
Oh, that's not true. There's nothing I want to do.
事實是, 我不想出力
I see.
好的
Thanks very much.
謝謝
-Is this your son? -Yeah, his name is Ross.
-是你兒子嗎？ -對, 他叫羅斯
-What? -Nothing, it's just that it's close to Ron.
-怎麼了？ -沒什麼, 跟Ron很接近嘛
Does little Ross like dinosaurs, by any chance?
這小小羅斯對恐龍有興趣嗎？
Yeah, they're all he talks about. Why?
是的, 他老是說起 那又怎麼樣？
How would he like to come with me to the Museum of Natural History..
他是否願意和我到自然歷史博物館
after everyone else has left, just the two of us..
在其他人都離開之後, 就剩我們兩個
and he can touch anything he wants?
他想摸哪裡就摸哪裡
I just heard it how you must have heard it, and that's not good.
我說的, 你都聽到了  不是那麼回事
Let me start again. I'm a paleontologist.
讓我再說一遍  我是古生物學家
You'll be there with us, and the touching refers only to bones.. fossils!
你也可以在場 摸的只會是骨頭和化石
-You could really arrange that? -You let Rachel come back and it's done.
-你真的可以安排到嗎？ -如果你能讓瑞秋回來, 那就這麼定了
I guess having Rachel back wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
我想, 讓瑞秋回來, 不見得就是壞事
Yes! Thank you! This is great! Thank you so much.
太好了, 十分感謝
I swear, your kid's gonna have the time of his life.
我保證, 這是你的孩子終身難忘的經歷
That's great. I worry about little Ross.
太好了 我對他挺擔心的
He's always reading, collecting rocks and he's obsessed with dinosaurs.
他老是捧著書本, 收集石頭  完全被恐龍給迷住了
He'll be fine!
他會正常的
-Hey, Phoebe. -Hey.
-嘿, 菲比  -嘿
-Everything okay? -I'm just mad at my agent.
-你怎麼了？ -我在生我經理人的氣
Estelle? Why?
Estelle？為什麼？
There's a part in this TV movie that I would be perfect for..
有一部電視電影 其中的角色很合適我演...
and I didn't even get put up for it. She better have a good reason.
她沒有推薦我去 她必須告訴我原因
I'm guessing she does.
我想她是有原因的
Well, I wanna hear it, because she keeps doing this.
我想聽聽, 她老是這樣
No, wait, wait, wait! All right, I gotta go.
噢, 等等 我要先走了
Just listen. Promise me that you will wait a minute before you call her.
答應我, 等一會再打給她
Well, okay. Why?
為什麼？
Because a promise between friends means never having to give a reason.
因為, 朋友之間的諾言, 從不需要有原因
I love that saying!
我喜歡這句話
-Hello? -Joey, it's Estelle.
-嗨！ -喬伊, 我是Estelle
I was just gonna call you. That's weird.
我正想打電話給你 真古怪
It's a little coincidental, but believable.
這是巧合, 但是可信
Listen, I'm sure you're wondering why I didn't get you..
我想你肯定想知道, 我為什麼沒有安排你...
an audition for that TV movie.
為那部電視電影試鏡
Yeah, actually I am.
是的, 確實是的
I guess I dropped the ball there.
我想我失職了 哦！
That's it? You know, it seems like all you do lately is drop the ball.
就這樣？我最近老是失職
Don't take that tone with me. Who do you think you are?
不要這麼和我說話 你以為自己是誰？
Alan Lemon, the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic?
阿蘭 萊蒙？ 第一個獨自駕機飛越大西洋的黑人男性？
No, look, all I'm saying is you're my agent..
聽我說, 你是我的經理人...
and you're not getting me any auditions and I'm tired of it.
但是你沒有為我爭取到試鏡機會  我受夠了
What are you saying?
你這樣說什麼意思？
I'm saying that this isn't working for me anymore, okay, Estelle?
我意思是, 不能再這樣了  Estelle
You're fired. Goodbye.
你被解雇了 再見
Man, tough week for Estelle.
噢, 這個星期真折磨人
-Hi. -Hi.
-嗨  -嗨
Emma left her stuffed T. rex at my house.
艾瑪把這忘在我房間了
-You know she can't sleep without it. -Well, she's asleep now.
-沒這她可睡不著哦  -嗯, 她現在在睡覺呢
-Stop forcing that thing on her. -Okay.
-別再塞這玩意兒給她  -好的
You're not gonna believe what happened to me today!
哦, 你絕對不會相信今天發生的事
Ralph Lauren called and gave me my job back!
拉夫.勞倫公司打電話請我回去
-No! -I mean, it was the weirdest thing.
-不會吧  -這是多麼古怪呀
They fire me and then out of nowhere, they just hire me back.
他們先是解雇我 然後又無緣無故重新聘用我
I mean, that place must just be falling apart without me!
一定是沒我就不行了
-So you're not going to Paris? -No, I'm still going!
-那麼, 你不去巴黎了吧  -去呀 我還去
What?
什麼？！
Well, when the Louis Vuitton people found out..
好吧, 當Louis Vuitton公司發現
that Ralph Lauren wanted me back, they offered me more money!
拉夫.勞倫公司請我回去 他們就提高了我的報酬
Ross, isn't that great?
羅斯, 是不是太棒了？
Hi. We're buying the house next door. Could we just take a look around?
我們有意買下旁邊的那座房子  允許我們參觀一下這裡嗎？
Sure, I'm showing it to someone else right now, but please, look around.
當然可以  我剛好帶人來參觀, 你們進來吧
I feel like we're cheating on our house.
我感到這是對我們房子的不忠
If we cheat, shouldn't it be with a hot, younger house..
你會為了另一座年輕漂亮的房子...
that does stuff that our house won't do?
而對老房子不忠嗎？
Ours is so much better!
我們的比這裡更棒
This living room is smaller, the dining room looks like a cave.
客廳更小 飯廳像個洞穴
What a hole!
真受不了
-So, what do you think? -Love it!
-你們覺得怎麼樣？ -喜歡!
We already have one offer. I think the lady upstairs will make another one.
我們本來有一位買家 樓上的女士是另一位
They could be our neighbors. What are they like?
是我們的鄰居耶 他們是什麼樣的？
The woman upstairs is nice. She and her husband have two kids.
樓上這位女士很好, 她和丈夫有2個小孩
-He's on Wall Street, and she's a.. -Oh.. my.. God!
-丈夫在華爾街工作, 她是    -喔   天   呀
Sure.
沒錯
Hey, Joey, you wanna come with me to..?
喬伊, 你想和我去   ？
Are you okay?
你怎麼啦？
Yeah, I just feel bad about firing Estelle.
我為解雇Estelle的事難過
This has gotta be killing her.
她肯定傷心死了
No, that wouldn't kill her.
她不會因此死的
A coronary embolism might.
除非她有血栓塞
I don't know. She's gotta be taking it hard. I was her only client.
她心都碎了 我是她唯一的客戶
Except for this guy who eats paper.
那個會吃紙的傢伙除外
And I'm guessing he eats more money than he makes.
我猜他吃的錢比掙得多
Look, I know she's not a great agent, but she did stick with me for 10 years.
我明白她不是優秀的經理人, 但我們合作10年了
-I'm gonna call her and hire her again. -No, no, no! Don't call her.
-我要給她打電話, 重新僱傭她  -不   不   不要給她打電話,
-You wait for her to call you. -Why?
-你等她給你打電話  -為什麼？
Because patience is the road to understanding.
耐心是通向理解的大道
Which is the key to a happy heart.
那是得到快樂的關鍵
You blow me away.
你真讓人吃驚, 我服了
All right, so promise you're gonna wait for her to call you?
答應我, 你等她給你打電話
-I promise. -Okay.
-我答應你  -好的
And that means never having to give a reason.
這意味著, 從不需要有原因
What a small world!
這世界真小呀
And yet I never run into Beyonce.
我還沒碰到過Beyonce(碧昂絲)
You two know each other?
你們認識？
We go way back. Before Monica made an honest man out of him..
在莫妮卡認識他之前
Chandler used to be my little love muffin.
錢德是我的小甜甜
Don't judge me.
別審我
Why not? I do.
為什麼不?我要.
So are you guys thinking of getting this house too?
這麼說, 你們也想要買下一座房子
Are we gonna have a bidding war? I better warn you, I'm a toughie.
如果是要投標競價的話 我可要警告你了 我是流氓我怕誰
Don't.. Don't.. Don't..
哦, 不
Don't do that.
不要
No, actually, we are buying the house next door.
其實我打算買下隔壁那座房子
Why?
為...為什麼？
I don't know why.
我不知道為什麼
Oh, that decides it, then! I was on the fence.
那就這麼定了  本來我還在猶豫
But knowing that you two would be our neighbors?
沒想到我們會成為鄰居
Now we have to get it!
那我就買下來了
Ellen, we're gonna talk numbers.
艾倫, 我們去定下價錢
This cannot be happening.
怎麼會搞成這樣？
The realtor said another couple made an offer.
經紀人不是說還有 另外一對夫婦有意購買嗎？
Maybe the Janices won't get it! Maybe the other couple will.
珍妮絲可能就買不成了  另外的夫婦可能會買下
The only way that'll happen is if the other couple are the Hitlers!
這絕不可能發生 除非那是希特勒夫婦
Okay, okay! All right, what if we get both houses?
我們兩座房子都買下來, 怎麼樣？
-We can turn this one into a guesthouse! -That's a great idea!
-將這裡作為家庭旅館  -真是好主意
By the way, I don't mean to sound distasteful..
不過我想知道
but when did you start crapping money?
你從什麼時候開始愛亂花錢了
-You come up with an idea. -All right.
-好呀 那你來想辦法  -好啊
We've still got three hours till escrow closes on our house.
還有3個小時才簽約
-We can still get out. -But we love our house.
-我們現在取消還來得及  -我們喜歡這座房子
Will we love it so much with her next door?
你也同樣喜歡住在她隔壁嗎？
And she's gonna be louder out here too!
她還會在這大聲嚷嚷,
Just the crickets and, "Oh.. my.. God!"
討厭的"Oh.. my.. God!"
Okay. But if we don't get this house, she'll still show up wherever we go.
即使我們不買這座房子 她還是會在我們面前出現
At least if she's here, it eliminates the element of surprise.
她住在這, 起碼不會再嚇我們一跳
Never again will you have to hear the three words..
你不會再聽到那3個字
that make your balls jump back up inside your body!
連你的蛋蛋都被嚇得縮進去
Well, we have to do something. We can't have her living next door.
我們得想想辦法 不能就讓她住在隔壁
Oh, that does it too.
嗯, 這也會
Who is it?
誰？
It's me. Ron.
是我, Ron
Look, I know Rachel turned you down..
我知道瑞秋拒絕你了
but I think there's a way you might be able to get her to come back.
不過我有一個法子能讓她會來
This may surprise you, but rehiring fired employees is not my main job.
請你別見怪, 重新聘用已經解雇的員工 不是我主要的工作
Just hear me out.
先聽我說
How would you feel about offering her a raise?
給她提高薪酬, 你認為怎麼樣？
Not good, Ron.
不好 Ron
Perhaps I can persuade you.
可能我會說服你
What if you could give your son..
你希望送給你兒子
this genuine pterodactyl egg replica.
這麼一隻恐龍蛋嗎？
Wow! That's pretty cool.
哇, 這很不錯呀
So? Do we have a deal?
這麼說   我們成交了？
-Okay, you got it. -Yes! Yes!
-好的 你成功了  -太好了！
This is gonna make me very popular.
這會讓我很受歡迎
Believe me, the ladies, they love it.
喔, 相信我, 女士都喜歡它
I meant with my son.
我指的是我兒子
Good, because the ladies, not so much.
對 女士對它不感興趣
Joey, this is Al Zebooker, the guy who eats paper.
喬伊, 我是Al Zebooker, 那個吃紙的人
I'm sure you've heard that Estelle passed away.
相信你聽說了Estelle過世的消息
I wanted to let you know there 's a memorial for her..
我通知你參加追悼會
at the Westside Chapel tomorrow at 10.
在westside教堂, 明天10點
Hope you can make it.
希望你能來
Oh, my God.
天呀
-Hello? -Joey, it' s Estelle.
-你好? -喬伊, 我是Estelle
Estelle?
Yeah, I wanted to call and tell you that there's no hard feelings for firing me.
我打電話是要告訴你 我沒有因為你解雇我而感到傷心
Okay. I just.. I can't believe you're calling me.
好的 真難以置信你會打電話給我
I didn't think I should just drop by.
我覺得我不應該貿然造訪
No, no! Don't drop by! Don't drop by!
不, 不要來訪
Anyway, you did what you had to do. I'm okay.
總之, 你繼續做你的事 我很好
Can I ask you something?
能問你個問題嗎？
What's it like there?
你那邊怎麼樣？
It's all right.
還湊合
Look, kiddo, I gotta go.
我要掛了 祝你好運
Good luck with the career. You're gonna be huge!
你會飛黃騰達的
Thanks for everything, Estelle. Bye.
謝謝你Estelle 再見
"Out of area." Boy, I'll say!
不在服務區？！噢
Well, I just talked to Sid.
我們討論過了
We are definitely putting in an offer on the house.
我們要買下這座房子
And I'll bet we get it!
一定會成功的
The Hitlers will be so disappointed.
希特勒夫婦肯定會很失望
All right, I gotta run. Tell Monica I say goodbye.
我要先走了 幫我跟莫妮卡說再見
I'll see you later, neighbor.
我們回頭見, 鄰居
Wait!
等等
I just want you to know that I'm so happy you're going to be here.
我想告訴你  你住在這裡我很開心
Oh, me too!
噢, 我也是
Because..
因為這樣
that way..
這樣…
we can pick up where we left off.
我們就能再續前緣
I never stopped loving you.
我一直都愛著你
-Oh.. my.. -Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-喔   天    -好的, 好的, 好的
I want you.
我想你
I need you.
我愛你
I must have you, Janice Litman-Goralnik nee Hosenstein.
我要你, Janice Litman-Gorelnik ne Hosenstein (猶太人姓名)
Chandler, what are you talking about?
錢德, 你在說什麼啊？
Now that you live next door, we can be together every day.
你現在住在隔壁, 我們會每天在一起
Sid and Monica never have to know a thing.
莫妮卡根本不會察覺
I don't know what to say.
我不知道該說什麼
I mean, you know, obviously we have this heat between us.
很顯然, 我們之間還有熱情
Obviously.
很顯然
But I love my husband.
但我愛我的丈夫
And I know you love your wife.
我也知道你愛你的妻子
I don't think we should get this house now.
我現在認為我不應該買這座房子
Don't say that. Don't dangle the dream and take it away.
別這麼說, 別打破我們的美夢
Chandler, one of us has got to be strong.
錢德 我們其中必須有一個人立場要堅定
I understand.
我知道
Although..
儘管...
Maybe just one last moment of weakness.
最後就軟弱一次吧
Goodbye, Chandler Bing.
再見了, 錢德賓
They're never coming down now!
不會再出現啦
-Hi. -Hi!
-嘿  -嘿
You are never going to believe what happened to me today.
嘿, 你肯定不會相信今天的事
What?
是什麼？
Ralph Lauren called, again, and they offered me more money.
拉夫.勞倫公司又打電話來了  而且他們給我更高的報酬
-They did? -Yes! It was the weirdest thing.
-真的嗎？ -是的
Zelner called me and said, "We will do anything we can to get you back."
真的太古怪了  他們說願意以任何代價請我回去
And that I should thank some "Ron."
還說我應該為此感謝Ron
I don't even know what department that guy's in!
可我連他是誰都不知道
-So, what are you gonna do? -Well, I took it!
-那麼, 你決定要怎麼做？ -我接受了
That's great! So you're staying in New York!
這太好了 你會留在紐約
-You're excited, right? -You know.. Look, the money's great.
-你高興嗎？ -是的 報酬很優厚
-It's certainly the easier choice. -Right.
-是理所當然的選擇  -對呀
But, you know, I mean, was I looking forward to going to Paris? Sure.
我本來是盼望著去巴黎的
Was I excited about working in the fashion capital of the world?
為能在世界時裝之都工作而感到興奮
Oh, absolutely.
哦, 太棒了
Yeah, but you know, this is..
不過
It's fine. I'm fine going back to a job where I've pretty much..
這樣也不錯 重新回到原來的工作
gotten everything out of it that I possibly can.
我覺得還不錯  儘管我已經忘掉它了
I had no idea..
我不知道
I had no idea you were so excited about Paris.
我不知道你為巴黎如此著迷
I mean, you said you were scared.
你說過你感到害怕
I mean, it was "good" scared, though, you know?
我想這是良性的害怕
I mean, like "when I moved to New York" scared.
當我搬來紐約時, 我感到害怕
Or "when I found out I was gonna have Emma" scared.
當我發現懷上艾瑪時, 我感到害怕
But this is fine. This is gonna be good.
這很不錯啦, 能行的
You should go.
你應該去
What?
什麼？
It's what you want. You should go.
那是你希望做到的, 去吧
You really think so?
你真的這麼認為嗎？
I really do.
真的
But I already told Zelner that I would come back.
可是我已經答應了回去
I'm sure he'll understand.
我相信他會理解的
All right. All right! I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna go to Paris!
好的 我就這麼定了  我要去巴黎
-Yeah. -Yeah.
-好啊 -好啊
I'm going to Paris!
好啊, 我要去巴黎
-Thank you, Ross. -Yeah, yeah.
-謝謝你, 羅斯 -是啊
Oh, I'm so happy.
我太高興了
Then I'm happy too.
我也高興
Thank you all for coming.
謝謝你們的到來
We're here today to pay our respects to a wonderful agent..
我們相聚在此懷念一位優秀的經理人
and a beautiful woman.
一位美麗的女性,
Inside.
內在美
As Estelle's only two clients, we would like to say a few words.
作為Estelle僅有的兩位客戶 我們有話要說
Dude, where's my speech?
我的講稿上哪去了？
That is entertaining. Al Zebooker, everybody!
這麼做很有趣 各位, 這是Al Zebooker